{
    "id": "20571f51c59e460dbc9476d8bb769638",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The tornado …………………….. the house flat.",
            "description": "Laid can mean knocked down.",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "laid",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two examples, I prefer the ……………………",
            "description": "Latter is the opposite of former.",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .......................... lazy to clean house.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too...to...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The situation was ……………………. absurd that it was laughable.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so...that...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Lean meat is ………………………… than fatty meat.",
            "description": "Healthier is the comparative form of healthy. ",
            "answers": [
                "more healthy",
                "healthier",
                "more healthier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………… school in the middle of the year.",
            "description": "Left is the past simple form of leave.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "leaved",
                "lefted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our schedule leaves no ……………………… for unexpected delays.",
            "description": "Leeway means flexibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "leeway",
                "leevay"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the legitimate ………………………. to the throne.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hair",
                "heir",
                "air"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We took a …………………… stroll after dinner.",
            "description": "Leisure is a noun leisurely is the adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "leisure",
                "leisurely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you ………………………… me 10 dollars until payday?",
            "description": "To lend is to loan.",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "borrow",
                "take"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie had ………………………. success than expected.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. ",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "low",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ……………………….. applications than expected.",
            "description": "Fewer is used with plural nouns less is used with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}